# 吃半拉不过瘾 得吃一个
I am still craving after a half. I need to finish the entire one.
# 赶紧吃吧 不吃就没了
Hurry up before they are gone
# 韭菜盒子
Chives pocket
# 咱们今天的馅呢是
The ingredients of stuffing include
# 猪肉 虾仁 韭菜馅
Pork, shrimps and chives
# 你看葱花 他用的是大葱花
See the green onions? He is using the big green onions.
# 窍门在这呢吧
So that’s the trick
# 这葱太小了它还没有释放出香味
The small green onions don’t have enough flavor
# 它就糊掉了 要煸到金黄色
They get burnt too fast. We need to fry them till golden
# 它才能出这个味道
That’s when the flavor get out
# 就关火了
Turn off the heater now
# 酱油要炸一下
Soy sauce in the frying wok
# 让它充分的释放酱香味道
So that the sauce flavor can come out
# 好了
Alright
# 这个味道就出来了
There the flavor goes
# 酱油遇热起泡
The soy sauce starts to bubble when heated
# 迅速它就挥发出香味了
And the flavor comes out quickly
# 然后把它倒在旁边 晾一晾
Let’s put this aside and let it cool off
# 所以吃韭菜馅这葱一定煸熟放进去
For stuffing with chives, the green onions need to be fried
# 这放在旁边 晾一晾
Put this aside and cool off
# 面是和好了的
We have already made the dough
# 咱们选用的是中筋粉
We chose to use the medium gluten flour
# 一斤面是七两水
350 grams of water for every 500 grams of flour
# 和完之后要饧它十分钟
Let the dough rest for 10 minutes after mixing
# 然后拿手再揉一遍
Then we knead the dough once again
# 表面就润了之后再饧一会儿
After the dough has a smooth surface, let it rest again
# 不饧它还是有筋
The resting help soften the gluten
# 没法去做这个剂
Otherwise it is hard to make the rolls
# 把面和好之后咱们就开始要和这个馅
After the dough, let’s mix the stuffing
# 肥瘦猪肉 虾仁 姜米
Ground pork with some fat, shrimps and garlic pieces
# 姜还可以有祛寒 去腥味的作用
Garlic adds some spice to it and gets rid of the gamey smell
# 猪肉馅呢 往里边加点葱
Put some green onions in the ground pork
# 做好的酱油倒进去 已经凉了
Pour the soy sauce we made in there. It is already cooled down
# 猪肉虾仁馅呢
For the pork and shrimp stuffing
# 你不能颜色就太重了
We don’t make the color too dark
# 搁点酱油你不能搁老抽
Some soy sauce, but not the dark soy sauce
# 一点点加
Add the soy sauce in a few times
# 盐 三克
Three grams of salt
# 胡椒粉 两克
Two grams of pepper
# 这个还不能打得很软
The stuffing cannot be too watery right now
# 因为这韭菜还会出汤
Because the chives contain some water too
# 所以要黏乎一点
So let it be a little sticky for now
# 闻一下
Have a smell
# 行 这样呢
Alright
# 咱把这虾仁就放进去了
Now we can put the shrimps in
# 虾仁咱们方便的时候可以用
If you have much time
# 葱姜水先泡一下
Marinate the shrimps with garlic and green onions first
# 多洗两遍
Wash it a few more times too
# 刚剥完这种虾仁还有一些不干净的
The peeled shrimps can have filth
# 也有一些粘液
Like the mucus
# 然后把切好的韭菜倒进去
Then pour the cut chives in
# 其实吃虾馅搁韭菜是最好的
The shrimp goes perfectly with the chives
# 但是有的人可能不吃韭菜
But some people don’t like chives
# 咱们来点香油
Let’s have some sesame oil
# 包馅无论是饺子还是馅饼
For stuffing, either dumplings or pies
# 尽可能的咱们要使用不好料酒
Hold the cooking wine if you don’t know what you are doing
# 不要用了 因为它包在里边
Because it will be contained within
# 这个料酒不容易往外挥发
The alcohol is hard to evaporate
# 你掌握不好就别用了
Hold it if you are not sure
# 这大家伙要注意
Be careful guys
# 这就行了
This should be good
# 咱们弄面
Now let’s work with the dough
# 这个面三十多度三十五度的水
The water for the dough need to be from 30 to 35 degrees Celsius
# 然后一斤面七两水就和成这样了
Then a 10:7 flour water ratio will give you a dough like this
# 但是有点软
It’s a bit soft though
# 软的时候咱们上面掸一点薄面
When the dough is too soft, dust some excessive flour on there
# 咱把它拿出来它不粘手
So it doesn’t stick to your hands when you grab it
# 要硬了它就不好吃了
The hard dough will not make a good texture for the pocket
# 你看这盆也比较干净
Take a look, the pot is pretty clean as well
# 和好的面
When the dough is made
# 饧置十分钟十五分钟之后
After a 10-15 minutes rest
# 就不能再揉了 上劲了
We cannot knead the dough anymore
# 咱们做一个剂 六十克
Let’s make a roll, about 60 grams
# 六十克的面团
A 60 gram dough
# 咱们要把它擀到直径十二厘米大小
We will roll it to a diameter about 12 centimeters
# 这个面很软
The dough is soft
# 馅饼边上要薄一点
For pie wraps, the edge need to be thinner
# 中间要厚一点
The center need to be thicker
# 最后捏褶的时候
So that when we nip it together
# 它中间的疙瘩不会很大
The lump in the middle won’t be too big
# 我记得我小时候
When I was little
# 妈妈给我烙那个馅饼
The pies my mom made me
# 永远都是中间一大疙瘩一点馅没有
Always had a huge lump in the center, with no stuffing at all
# 十二（厘米）
Twelve centimeters
# 大约呢包上六十克的馅
With about 60 grams of stuffing
# 包的时候 捏这小边 一点点
When we wrap it, nip just a small tip of the edge slowly
# 转着圈的捏
Rotate and nip
# 你看它中间 它不是一大硬疙瘩
See the middle here, not a big lump
# 没那么大然后中间的时候捏一下
Nip it together in the middle to close it
# 可以往回盖一下 这样就可以了
And then push it back a bit, done
# 捏的时候注意 捏上边一点 一边
When we nip it, be careful to just nip a tiny bit
# 一点一点往起兜
Nip the bit up and then nip together
# 左手是往里填馅用的
Your left hand can push the stuffing in during the same time
# 如果冒出来了你就使手按它一下
If the stuffing is coming out, just push it back
# 中间它不是疙瘩
Not a lump in the middle
# 弄完之后咱们就要翻着放
Then we put it upside down after done
# 搁在面粉的案板上边
On a chopping board with flour on it
# 擀一下 轻点
Roll it very gently
# 看着要露馅了
When you see the stuffing is going to burst
# 翻过来 擀一擀
Flip it over and then roll
# 也擀到要露馅了 咱们就下锅
When the stuffing is going to come out on the other too, it is ready to cook
# 薄面抖一抖
Dust the excessive flour off
# 今天我们使平底锅来煎馅饼
We are frying our pockets with a pan
# 如果我们在家要是用电饼铛烙
We may also be cooking with an electrical pan fryer
# 咱们家庭式的电饼铛 槽比较浅
The ones in families have a rather thinner groove
# 热饼铛 放进去之后
So that when we put the pockets in
# 馅饼表面的淀粉 面粉
The starch and flour at the surface of the pockets
# 迅速糊化凝结成壳了
Will get burnt and sealed
# 馅儿里边遇热 它会出起鼓来
The stuffing inside will inflate when heated
# 如果说您馅饼特别厚
If you made the pockets thick
# 它在起鼓的时候
When they inflate
# 电饼铛的盖 就会影响它长
The cap of the electrical pan fryer will pressure on them
# 这时候它就会从两边会露馅
Then the stuffing will come out from the edges
# 就破了 就顶破了
They will break the shape
# 所以要用饼铛的话最好不要太厚
So if you are cooking with those electrical pan fryers, do not make the pockets too thick
# 跟饼铛的槽一样高
At most as think as the groove when cooked
# 如果是生胚的话 会矮到一半
Which is half as thick before cooking
# 盖上盖 盖上盖歇一会
Put the lid on
# 盖盖煮皮 盖盖烙皮
With the lid, the pan cooks the wraps
# 馅饼的表面起鼓了
When the surface starts to inflate
# 证明里面的肉蔬菜还有虾都熟了
It means the meat, veggies and the shrimps in there are cooked
# 它只有熟了以后
They can only generate the steam
# 它才能产生热的蒸汽
After they are cooked
# 出锅啦
Ready to get out
# 韭菜盒子
Chives pockets
# 你们得吃一个
You guys have to try an entire one
# 半拉不够吃
Half of it won’t get you satisfied
# 吃半拉不过瘾 得吃一个
You will still be carved after half, finish it in whole
# 赶紧吃吧 不吃就没了
Hurry up before they are all gone
# 这是虾肉 这大虾肉
See the shrimp here, big pieces
# 我也看得嘴馋了 你也来一个
I’m hungry too. Try one too
# 摄影师也尝一个 元国来一个吃
Let’s have one for our photographer and Yuanguo
# 这馅饼香
The pocket is so good
# 特别是酱油 它炸这葱花
Especially for the soy sauce. The green onions fried is exceptional
# 呲的熟油 这熟油呢
The oil added in the stuffing is cooked
# 真的 一个是非常提鲜
Really improves the aroma
# 虾跟韭菜绝搭
The shrimp goes perfectly with chives
# 这盘吃完了 上菜
We are done with this plate. We need more
# 接着上 第二盘
There you go, second plate